Nahid Jahani Web Developer

Personal Info

Addressee:4353 Halifax St. Burnaby Phone Number: 6044419287

Email: Jahaninahide@Gmail.com

Portfolio:

https://nahid-jahani.github.io/

Nahid-jahani-Protfolio

LinkedIn:

http://linkedin.com/in/nahid-

jahani- 709134145

Soft Skills

Great at Problem solving

Collaborations

Time management

Good Leadership

Technical Skills

JavaScript

HTML

C#

React.js

WordPress

Languages

English

Farsi

Turkish

Career Objective

Joiner web Developer with more than 3 years of experience in designing and developing web design, testing, and training staff technologies. Well-versed in numerous programing languages including JavaScript, React, HTML, CSS, CorelDraw, Adobe and Photoshop. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

Proficient Skills

- Strong organization and communications skills.
- o Curate effective content to communicate brand messages in fresh, reactive ways.
- o Self-motivated with outstanding time management.
- Attentive listening and effective oral communication skills
- Understanding of labor regulations and legal codes.

Experience

Web Developer Faith Fire Surrey, BC 2021- present

- Plan website development, converting mock-ups into usable web presence with HTML, JavaScript and CSS coding.
- Develop functional digital design concepts across various platforms to strengthen company brand and identity.
- Strengthen organizational intranet program and sub-sites to bolster internal communication strategies.
- Implement website maintenance, content management, update and security resource tutorials to assist end-user training.

Web Designer Shirin Asal, Co Tabriz, Iran 2010-2014

- Developed project concepts and maintain workflow.
- Contacted clients to obtain more information and discussed designed options.
- Employed mastery of designer languages

Education

Bachler of Software Engineer 2006-2010 Jahad Daneshgahi, Tabriz, Iran

Certificates

C#, Html, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery BCIT 2019-2021 React.js, WordPress UDEMY 2020- 2021